in today's video of how to guide I'm
going to show you how to login to your
Manulife account
whether you're trying to log in to any
of your accounts such as banking
insurance or investment with manual life
let me show you the section from where
you can log in to either of those
accounts
if this video sounds helpful to you then
make sure you stick till the end
search for manulife.ca on the search bar
of your web browser
once you're on the website of Manulife
to log into your account click on sign
in on the top right
from the sign in section you can see all
of the accounts that you can log into
such as insurance Investments and bank
accounts
so pick the account that you're trying
to log in and then just click on the
sign in option
once you click on sign in it's going to
take you to the sign in form where
you'll need to type in your username of
your account that you created and also
type in the password
if you're having any difficulties
logging in because you forgot your
username or the password of your account
you can click on the forgot username
link or the forgot password link from
there you'll be able to recover both of
these information
and lastly you can also check this box
which says Remember Me this Way do not
need to type in your username each time
you visit this website so once you type
in both of these information you can
click on sign in and you'll be signed in
to your manual life account whether you
have any type of account
so that was a short and easy video If
this video was helpful to you be sure to
give this video a thumbs up and also
subscribe to our channel for more daily
videos that we upload
that's pretty much it for today's video
thanks for watching